Man:
Excuse me.
Would you mind if I asked you some questions?
We’re doing a survey on transport.
Sadie:
Yes,
that’s OK.
Man:
First of all, can I take your name?
Sadie:
Yes.
It’s Sadie Jones.
Man:
Thanks very much.
And could I have your date of birth – just the year will do, actually.
Is that all right?
Sadie:
Yes,
that’s fine.
It’s 1991.
Man:
So next your postcode, please.
Sadie:
It’s DW30 7YZ.
Man:
Great.
Thanks.
Is that in Wells?
Sadie:
No it’s actually in Harborne – Wells isn’t far from there, though.
Man:
I really like that area.
My grandmother lived there when I was a kid.
Sadie:
Yes, it is nice.
Man:
Right,
so now I want to ask you some questions about how you travelled here
today.
Did you use public transport?
Sadie:
Yes.
I came by bus.
Man:
OK.
And that was today.
It’s the 24th of April, isn’t it?
Sadie:
Isn’t it the 25th?
No, actually, you’re right.
Man:
And what was the reason for your trip today?
I can see you’ve got some shopping with you.
Sadie:
Yes.
I did some shopping but the main reason I came here was to go
to the dentist.
Man:
That’s not much fun.
Hope it was nothing serious.
Sadie:
No, it was just a check-up.
It’s fine.
Man:
Good.
Do you normally travel by bus into the city centre?
Sadie:
Yes.
I stopped driving in ages ago because parking was so difficult to find
and it costs so much.
Man:
I see.
Sadie:
The bus is much more convenient too.
It only takes about 30 minutes.
Man:
That’s good.
So where did you start your journey?
Sadie:
At the bus stop on Claxby Street.
Man:
Is that C-L-A–X-B-Y?
Sadie:
That’s right.
Man:
And how satisfied with the service are you?
Do you have any complaints?
Sadie:
Well, as I said, it’s very convenient and quick when it’s on
time,
but this morning it was late.
Only about 10 minutes,
but still.
Man:
Yes, I understand that’s annoying.
And what about the timetable?
Do you have any comments about that?
Sadie:
Mmm.
I suppose I mainly use the bus during the day,
but any time I’ve been in town in the evening – for dinner
or at the cinema – I’ve noticed you have to wait a long time
for a bus – there aren’t that many.
Man:
OK, thanks.
So now I’d like to ask you about your car use.
Sadie:
Well, I have got a car but I don’t use it that often.
Mainly just to go to the supermarket.
But that’s about it really.
My husband uses it at the weekends to go to the golf club.
Man:
And what about a bicycle?
Sadie:
I don’t actually have one at the moment.
Man:
What about the city bikes you can rent?
Do you ever use those?
Sadie:
No – I’m not keen on cycling there because of all the pollution.
But I would like to get a bike – it would be good to
use it to get to work.
Man:
So why haven’t you got one now?
Sadie:
Well, I live in a flat – on the second floor
and it doesn’t have any storage – so we’d have to leave it in
the hall outside the flat.
Man:
I see.
OK.
Well, I think that’s all ...